goregrish.com 2019-11-15

# Goregrish Privacy Policy

ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE

GoreGrish.com is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing GoreGrish.com you acknowledge and fully understand GoreGrish.com Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.

DISCLOSURE

GoreGrish.com will never email you unless you emailed us first, or you have subscribed to posts & messages via the forums, or if we have questions regarding your uploads. We do not give, sell or make any use of our email database.

COOKIE USAGE. We believe that your experience of the site would be adversely affected if you opted out of the cookies we use.

**This page discusses how cookies are used by this site.**

If you continue to use this site, you are consenting to our use of cookies.

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small text files stored on your computer by your web browser at the request of a site you're viewing. This allows the site you're viewing to remember things about you, such as your preferences and history or to keep you logged in. Cookies may be stored on your computer for a short time (such as only while your browser is open) or for an extended period of time, even years. Cookies not set by this site will not be accessible to us.

**Our cookie usage**

This site uses cookies for numerous things, including:

__Registration and maintaining your preferences. This includes ensuring that you can stay logged in and keeping the site in the language or appearance that you requested.

__Analytics. This allows us to determine how people are using the site and improve it.

__Advertising cookies (possibly third-party). If this site displays advertising, cookies may be set by the advertisers to determine who has viewed an ad or similar things. These cookies may be set by third parties, in which case this site has no ability to read or write these cookies.

__Other third-party cookies for things like Facebook or Twitter sharing. These cookies will generally be set by the third-party independently, so this site will have no ability to access them.

**Additional cookies and those set by third parties**

Additional cookies may be set during the use of the site to remember information as certain actions are being performed, or remembering certain preferences. Other cookies may be set by third party service providers which may provideinformation such as tracking anonymously which users are visiting the site, or set by content embedded into some pages, such as YouTube or other media service providers.

**Removing/disabling cookies**

Managing your cookies and cookie preferences must be done from within your browser's options/preferences. To learn more about cookies, and find more information about blocking certain types of cookies, please visit the [ICO website Cookies page](https://ico.org.uk/your-data-matters/online/cookies/).

What information we collect

**When using any products and services provided by Goregrish.com, we may require some or all of the following information:**

__Username.

__Email Address.

Additionally, whilst using the Goregrish.com website, any associated websites and sub-domains, some or all of the following information may be collected:

__Internet Protocol (IP) address.

__geographical location.

__browser type and version.

__operating system.

__referral source.

__length of visit, page views, website navigation and any other related browsing activity.

What we do with the information we collect

**The information you provide to Goregrish.com is required for, but not limited to, the following reasons:**

__access to the Goregrish.com website, associated websites and sub-domains.

__account management.

__Account confirmation and account reset.

__confirmation of email address from members.

__sending notices of news, notices and other relevant forum software communications.

Links to other websites

Goregrish.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, may contain links to other websites. These websites may or may not be affiliated with Goregrish.com. When you access third party websites, you do so at your own risk.

Controlling your personal information

When using the Goregrish.com forum, you may choose to limit public viewing of applicable personal information through the settings located in the Privacy section of your account. Goregrish.com will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your explicit permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you information only pertaining to Goregrish.com, or your account. If you discover any of the information Goregrish.com holds for you is incorrect or incomplete, that you are unable to change yourself, please contact us as soon as possible so the necessary changes can be made.
